Hello everyone, this is Haruka Koizumi, aka Oharu.
Yes, so today, I answered a question from Kanamin!
Yes, so I've been doing a project where 22-year-old Oharu answers 5 questions that I recently received from other members, and this is the 4th installment!
This time, I'd like to answer Kanamin's question. Thank you Kanamin for sending me your question.
I'd like to answer your questions right away.
The birthday that left the biggest impression on you is...
I wonder...
I don't know.
Most memorable birthday?
Hmmm...
Hmm...
But I guess...
The birthday when I turned 20.
I think it's the most memorable birthday.
I was 20 years old...
I'm an adult.
It's a grown-up year.
I remember the birthday when I became an adult.
And right after that was my coming-of-age ceremony, so I had already done the pre-shoots and all that.
I was thinking about what I wanted to wear on that day.
I was thinking about how I wanted to spend the coming-of-age ceremony, and how I wanted to spend the coming-of-age ceremony.
I had a lot of fun being excited about it.
Yes, I did.
Did you buy any gifts for yourself?
What? No, I didn't.
Did I buy anything?
I don't think I bought any tampres.
Last year or the year before...
Givenchy.
Lantern Borel.
Lantern Borel Blossom.
Lantern Borel Blossom, a little expensive cosmetics.
I bought it for my
I bought it for my birthday.
But I don't think I bought anything this year.
I haven't bought anything this year.
Maybe I'll go buy something when I get settled.
Okay, number three.
What kind of cake do you like?
Well, there's cake, and I like it a lot.
You've been here before, haven't you?
You must be Nichan.
What's your favorite cake?
I like basically anything.
But the other day, in the Valentine's Day video...
Strawberry Candle
which is a strawberry and chocolate cake.
I had a piece of strawberry and chocolate cake called Strawberry Candle.
It made me want to eat more chocolate cake.
I've been wanting to eat more chocolate cake this year.
But there are so many cake shops I want to go to.
I've already found a few that I want to go back to.
I'd like to go again.
I'll report back when I get there.
Yes, this is the fourth one already!
The fourth one.
What do you want to challenge yourself at the age of 22?
The first thing I want to try is swimming.
I can't swim, so swimming.
And bouldering?
I want to boulder.
I also want to become a better cook.
And, um, swimming.
If I can swim...
I'd like to go swimming
I'd like to go swimming in Okinawa or something.
I'd like to do skydiving or something like that.
I want to do that.
That's why I want to do it.
I don't know if I'm actually going to do it or not.
If I say I want to do something, I can say a lot of things.
What else would be good?
What would be good... what would be good...
I wonder what would be good.
I don't know what's good.
Let's see...
It's a challenge, right?
Mm-hmm.
But, you know, I've grown to love exercise.
So I want to do a lot of exercise-related things.
I want to do a lot of things related to exercise.I'd like to do a lot of
I don't know.
I don't know, it was great in the past and it's still great now.
I'm not a good athlete.
I'm rather bad at it.
That's why I used to hate exercise.
But now I like it even though I'm not good at it.
That's the dance of Jikken.
I've learned to dance a lot through Jikken.
I started to like exercise.
I want to do something related to exercise
I want to do something related to exercise.
So I've become interested in sports and exercise.
I hope to have an active year.
Lastly, number 5.
Do you drink Compota, which you used to be addicted to?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You like it?
Compota? Yeah, but it's getting cold out, so...
I'm drinking a lot of it.
I do.
But I used to be all about warm compotas, but lately I've been flirting with cold compotas.
I'm also into ume paste and chocolate butts... I think I'm getting a little tired of those... and they're kind of the same... I got this stamp.
Bewooon!
See? It says "Bewon" on it... so they are similar... thanks for the question Kanami! Thanks for the question Kanami! And my sister did it for me.
It's a bear's hair!
Yes! So, that's it.
Next time, I will be the last member to ask a question in this project.
Next time, or rather, the last time, I asked Hito-chan a question.
HITO-chan asked me a question, and I'd like to answer it.
I would like to answer them.
I hope you enjoy the last part of this project!
If you liked this video, please click the "Good" button and subscribe to our channel!
And please let us know what stamps you use most often.
See you next time!
Bye bye!